<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="flowers">Flowers</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks/Outdoors</string>
    <string name="schools">Schools</string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="cultural">Cultural</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="description_general">description goes here</string>
    <string name="description_thornden">
        Centrally located. Thornden Park offers a place to cool off on hot summer days, either in the pool,
        or strolling under the many shade trees. The park also has a basket ball court, and an outdoor amphitheater that hosts activities often.
        Great place to walk the dog or sled in the winter time.
    </string>
    <string name="description_burnet">A large park located on the west side of the city, it is also
    home to the Burnet Park Zoo. The zoo is very popular with locals, among the favorite animals to
    visit are the African lions, the grey and red wolves, and the Siberian tigers.
    </string>
    <string name="description_erie">The towpaths of the old Erie Canal waterway system are
    today enjoyable as great destinations for biking, hiking and jogging. The canals criss cross the
    state of New York, many open to boating and cruises as well. Green Lakes hosts a beach which is
    very popular during the hot days of summer</string>
    <string name="description_jamesville">The town of Jamesville on the periphery of the city is nestled
    in hills, and there are also many small farms. Jamesville beach is a quick retreat for a picnic. For
    the adventurous, the annual Syracuse Balloonfest launches from Jamesville Beach providing a great
        way to view the spectacular scenery of the region from above.</string>
    <string name="description_clark">On the south eastern edge of the city is found Clark Reservation.
    An ancient glacial lake lies at the bottom of a large gorge, which is blanketed in trees,
        boulder formations,and trails. Walking into Clark Reservation seems like stepping back into time.
        One could easily imagine the whole of New York State was forest like this at some time. It is a great
        place to find some soothing quiet as well as view flora and fauna such as maple trees, migrating monarch
        butterflies, robins, wild turkeys, white-tailed deer and foxes. One would half expect to hear the
        howl of wolves, maybe someday they will make their way back down from Canada to their former ranges.
    </string>

    <string name="spaghetti_phone">13154751807</string>
    <string name="creole_soul_phone">13155304178</string>
    <string name="pavones_pizza_phone">13154711980</string>
    <string name="koto_grill_phone">13154795686</string>
    <string name="rescue_phone">13154726251</string>
    <string name="wings_syracuse_phone">13154459464</string>
    <string name="hk_takeout_phone">13154288898</string>


    <string name="description_creole">Have you got a taste for cajun catfish? Maybe
    the thought of gumbo, fried okra or jambalaya makes you say ohhhhh ouiiiii!? If so, this is the spot
    for you.</string>
    <string name="description_rescue">If you happen to find yourself broke, or homeless, or both that
    does not mean you should not eat some quality food while in Syracuse. The Rescue Mission has been
    serving the food needs of people having hard times for decades. Give it a try you might like it.</string>
    <string name="description_koto">Located in the very popular Destiny USA mall food court, this restaurant
         has a unique and distinct presence. Koto is popular for the quality Japanese cuisine it serves.
        Say "いただきます(i-ta-da-ki-mas)" directly before eating to get a smile from the chef.</string>
    <string name="description_pavones">Just straight forward, delicious, NY style pizza here at reasonable pricing. </string>
    <string name="description_spaghetti">The Spaghetti Warehouse is tucked away in a section of town that was
    formerly factories and warehouses. These buildings have been converted to salons, upscale apartments, and retail stores.
    It has a very cozy environment. Do not be surprised if a theatrical group, a magician, or possibly a violinist is presented
    during your meal. </string>

    <string name="poi_name_key">poiName</string>
    <string name="address_key">address</string>
    <string name="poisearch_hint">Kind of place to add to your route</string>
    <string name="no_search_results">No search results for \'%1$s\'. Please try another search term.</string>
    <string name="add_to_my_route">Add to my route</string>

    <string name="geocode_no_results">No Geocoder results. Pick different location and try again.</string>
    <string name="api_response_error">API response error: \'%1$s\'.</string>
</resources>